<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EZ Mail PresUniv</string>
    <string name="president">President&#160;</string>
    <string name="university">University</string>
    <string name="academic_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The Academic Bureau at President University is a key administrative department that manages several critical academic processes and
        documentation for students. Here are the details of the services they provide:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Enrollments Schedule:</b> They manage and communicate the schedule for course enrollments.</li>
            <li><b>Class Schedule:</b> They organize and distribute the timetable for all classes.</li>
            <li><b>GPA:</b> They handle the recording and reporting of students\' Grade Point Averages.</li>
            <li><b>Diploma &amp; Transcript:</b> They issue official academic transcripts and diplomas.</li>
            <li><b>Resign:</b> They process student resignations from the university.</li>
            <li><b>Drop Out:</b> They manage the formalities for students who wish to discontinue their studies.</li>
            <li><b>Academic Leave:</b> They handle requests for academic leave of absence.</li>
            <li><b>General Document Request:</b> They provide various academic-related documents upon request.</li>
            <li><b>Judicium Clearance:</b> They manage the clearance process for students who are about to graduate.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="finance_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The Finance and Accounting Bureau at President University is responsible for managing financial matters related to students. Here\'s a detailed list of their responsibilities:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Tuition Fee:</b> Handling payments related to students\' tuition.</li>
            <li><b>Installment:</b> Managing installment plans for tuition fee payments.</li>
            <li><b>Late Payment:</b> Addressing issues related to late payments.</li>
            <li><b>Outstanding Payment Validation for Enrollment:</b> Validating payments for enrollment purposes.</li>
            <li><b>Financial Assistance:</b> Providing information and managing applications for financial aid.</li>
            <li><b>Extension Fee:</b> Processing fees for extension of study periods.</li>
            <li><b>Thesis Defense Fee:</b> Managing payments for thesis defense sessions.</li>
            <li><b>Graduation Enrollment Fee:</b> Handling fees related to graduation procedures.</li>
            <li><b>Student Resignation Fee:</b> Processing fees for students who resign from the university.</li>
            <li><b>Academic Leave Fee:</b> Managing fees for academic leave.</li>
            <li><b>Other Payment Matters:</b> Addressing various other payment-related issues.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="icc_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The Internship and Career Center (ICC) at President University is a department that handles matters related to professional development and
        internships for students. Here are the main responsibilities of the ICC:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Professional Stream:</b> Managing and providing guidance on professional streams, which are career pathways for students.</li>
            <li><b>Internship Program:</b> Overseeing all aspects of the internship program, including placements, coordination with companies, and ensuring that students gain valuable work experience.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="ellc_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The English Language and Literature Center (ELLC), previously known as the Culture and Language Center (CLC),
        is a department at President University that focuses on English language services. Here are the services provided by ELLC:

        <ul>
            <li><b>President English Test (PET):</b> Administration of the English proficiency test.</li>
            <li><b>FREE English-tutoring service:</b> For students who want to improve their English skills.</li>
            <li><b>Translation/proofreading certificate:</b> Available for Lecturers/Staffs Only.</li>
            <li><b>English competency score validation:</b> Validation of English proficiency scores.</li>
            <li><b>Minimum standard for English proficiency:</b> Setting and validating the minimum English proficiency standards for students.</li>
            <li><b>Judicium clearance validation on English Proficiency:</b> Ensuring students meet the English proficiency requirements for graduation.</li>
            <li><b>English proficiency development program:</b> Programs designed to help students improve their English language skills.</li>
            <li><b>Non-credits English subjects:</b> Offering English subjects that do not count towards credit requirements but aid in language proficiency.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="ga_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The General Affairs (GA) Office at President University is tasked with several important operational functions to
        support the university\'s daily activities and special events. Here are more details about their responsibilities:

        <ul>
            <li><b>COVID-19 Task Force:</b> They manage and implement measures to prevent and control COVID-19 on campus, ensuring the health and safety of the university community.</li>
            <li><b>Classroom Arrangement:</b> They organize and schedule the use of classrooms to accommodate the academic needs of students and faculty.</li>
            <li><b>Transportation Arrangement for Campus Events:</b> They coordinate transportation for various campus events, ensuring that logistics are handled efficiently.</li>
            <li><b>Bus Schedule:</b> They manage the schedule of the campus bus service, providing students and staff with reliable transportation options.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="sa_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The Student Affairs (SA) Bureau at President University plays a vital role in enriching the student experience beyond the classroom. Here are more details about their functions and services:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Kampus Merdeka:</b> They facilitate and provide consultation for students interested in participating in the Kampus Merdeka program,
            which is a government initiative offering various learning opportunities outside the university curriculum.</li>
            <li><b>Non-Academic Activities:</b> The SA Bureau organizes and supports a range of non-academic activities that contribute to students\' personal growth and leadership skills.</li>
            <li><b>Competitions:</b> They assist and guide students who wish to participate in various competitions, both at the national and international levels,
            promoting the university\'s presence and students\' talents.</li>
            <li><b>Student Organizations:</b> The SA Bureau oversees student organizations, helping them plan and execute events and activities that enhance campus life.</li>
            <li><b>Student Development:</b> They offer programs and workshops aimed at developing students\' soft skills and preparing them for their future careers.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="io_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The International Office (IO) at President University is a hub for international affairs and services, catering to both local and international students. Here are more details about their functions:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Scholarship Stream:</b> They provide information and assistance to students seeking scholarships for international programs, including study abroad opportunities.</li>
            <li><b>Student Visa:</b> The IO assists international students with obtaining and renewing their student visas, ensuring they maintain legal status during their studies in Indonesia.</li>
            <li><b>Student Exchange Program:</b> They manage partnerships with universities around the world and coordinate the exchange programs,
            allowing students to study part of their degree at a partner institution.</li>
            <li><b>KITAS (Stay Permit):</b> The IO helps international students with the process of obtaining and renewing their KITAS,
            which is the official stay permit required for long-term residency in Indonesia.</li>
            <li><b>Other Matters Related to Foreign Students:</b> The IO serves as a support center for international students,
            providing guidance on various issues such as cultural adaptation, legal matters, and any other challenges they may face while studying in Indonesia.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="alumni_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The Alumni Relations Bureau at President University is dedicated to maintaining a strong connection between the university and its alumni.
        Here are the key functions and services provided by the Alumni Relations Bureau:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Alumni Reunion:</b> They organize reunions for alumni to reconnect with their peers and the university.</li>
            <li><b>President University Tracer Study:</b> They conduct surveys to track the career progression and impact of alumni in the workforce,
            which is part of the university\'s obligation to the government.</li>
            <li><b>Alumni Liaison:</b> The bureau serves as a point of contact for alumni to communicate with the university, offering support and facilitating engagement in various activities.</li>
        </ul>

        The Alumni Relations Bureau also provides information and assistance with other alumni-related requests, such as:

        <ul>
            <li><b>Diploma and Transcript Legalization:</b> Alumni can request legalized copies of their diploma and transcript.</li>
            <li><b>Other Document Request:</b> Alumni can request other documents related to their academic and administrative records.</li>
            <li><b>Tracer Study Participation:</b> Alumni are invited to participate in tracer studies to provide feedback on their educational experience and career development.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dewan_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The President University Ethics Board, or "Dewan Etik," is an important body that ensures all members of the university community adhere to established ethical standards.
        The board handles issues related to misconduct and ethical breaches by both students and lecturers.<br><br>
        The Ethics Board is composed of a Chairperson, Members, and a Secretariat. They are responsible for investigating complaints, enforcing the code of ethics,
        and ensuring a safe and respectful environment for learning and teaching.<br><br>
        You can contact the Dewan Etik (Ethics Board) at President University for the following reasons:<br><br>
        <b>For Lecturers\' Violations:</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Acts that defame the honor and reputation of the university.</li>
            <li>Failure to fulfill academic obligations (Tri Dharma Perguruan Tinggi).</li>
            <li>Abuse of power in academic or non-academic activities.</li>
            <li>Sexual harassment, either physical or psychological.</li>
            <li>Plagiarism in scientific research.</li>
            <li>Unfair treatment towards students or colleagues.</li>
            <li>Romantic relationships with students.</li>
            <li>Any other acts that violate Indonesian laws and regulations.</li>
        </ul>

        <b>For Students\' Violations:</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Academic dishonesty, such as plagiarism or document forgery.</li>
            <li>Acts of disrespect towards any religion or belief.</li>
            <li>Sexual misconduct, including harassment and pornography.</li>
            <li>Violent crimes, theft, or distribution of illegal substances.</li>
            <li>Possession or use of weapons or narcotics within the university area.</li>
            <li>Destruction of university property or unauthorized use of facilities.</li>
            <li>Wearing clothing that is considered indecent or offensive.</li>
            <li>Any other acts that are prohibited under Indonesian law.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dev_desc">
        <![CDATA[
        The developer EZ Mail PresUniv, the app you are currently interacting with, is the group of Wireless Mobile Programming from Cyber Security Class 1.<br><br>
        The developer consists of 4 students from the class of 2022, they are:

        <ul>
            <li>Muhammad Yusuf (001202200028) as <b>Leader</b></li>
            <li>Muhammad Fairuz Suhendi (001202200115) as <b>Member</b></li>
            <li>Kemal muhammad fathan (001202200119) as <b>Member</b></li>
            <li>Arius Aurelius (001202200040) as <b>Member</b></li>
        </ul>

        They handle the development, management, and maintenance of this app.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pusc_desc">
        <![CDATA[
    Hello, Presunivers!✨<br><br>

    In our commitment to enhance the President University student experience by providing the necessary facilities, the President University Student Council (PUSC) 2024
    invites you to share your suggestions, feedback, and critiques during the PAY ATTENTION period, from December 1st to 20th, 2023.<br><br>

    Your input is valuable, and we encourage you to contribute as every voice matters in shaping our university environment.<br><br>

    Best regards,<br>
    PUSC 2024
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="computing_desc">
    <![CDATA[
    Hello Computizen!👋🏻<br>
    Hope everything is okay🤗<br><br>

    We\'re here to let you know that we\'re starting Aspirations Week!🤩<br><br>

    Is there anything you want to say about the faculty of computing?🤔<br>
    If you have, let\'s together make our faculty better by filling out our aspiration form, dear Computizen!📝<br><br>

    In the aspiration column, Computizen doesn\'t have to write down personal identity (name/major) and Computizen is free to give honest aspirations, suggestions, ideas, or
    constructive criticism in a form‼️<br><br>

    ⭐️Let\'s together make our faculties even better by filling out the link below<br><br>

    Best regards,<br>
    PUFA Computing❤️
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="emailSubject">Specific Information or Topic You Are Talking About</string>
    <string name="emailBody">Dear Mr/Mrs [Departement Name],\n\n
    I hope this email finds you well. My name is [Your Full Name], and I am from [Your Major] batch [Your Batch]. I am writing to talk about [specific information or topic you are talking about].\n\n
    [Provide information on the purpose of your email and any context needed for the recipient to understand your question].\n\n
    I would greatly appreciate it if you could provide me with the necessary information or direct me to the appropriate department or individual who can assist me.\n\n
    Thank you very much for your time and assistance. I look forward to your prompt response.\n\n
    Best regards,\n\n
    [Your Full Name]\n
    [Your Student ID]</string>
</resources>
